PAIGE RICKERT

□ pg-g.github.io

dithub.com/pg-g dithub.com/pg-g dithub.com/pg-g

y pg_g

□ paigegu3@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Front end developer with 5 years of experience, including 3+ years managing corporate websites. Main tools include HTML, CSS, LESS, Javascript, with a working knowledge of PHP. Passionate about organizing, learning, communication, and building a great product.

EXPERIENCE

2015-17 Web Developer

Instructure

- Maintained and developed all of company's domestic and international marketing websites, which included integrating advanced lead gen and other functionality (HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript)
- Responsible for setting up email, landing page, blog, and form templates in Hubspot and Marketo
- Notable projects: Arc product website (arcmedia.com), Canvas product's LATAM and Brazil presences (canvaslms.com/brasil & canvaslms.com/latam), Bridge product's Learning Center hub (getbridge.com/lc)

2014-15

Creative Lead / Web Developer

Jive Communications

- Designed, developed, and managed company website (jive.com) built on Wordpress (HTML, LESS, PHP) with Bootstrap.
- Managed and developed company brand, including visual and voice.
- Supervised and aided in creation of content including print collateral, website material, videos, social media strategy, blog content, tradeshow assets, etc.

2012-14

Multimedia Specialist

Jive Communications

- · Redesigned and rebuilt company website.
- · Maintained both internal and user-facing knowledgebase and wiki; created customer training materials (PDFs, charts, videos).
- Created and designed collateral for marketing, website, company identity, internal use, etc.

2012

Organic Internet Marketer

SkyRocket Inc.

- Developed js-based web app for marketing campaign.
- Created content (wrote articles and created graphics) for company-owned and client blogs.

2010-11

Senior Software Instructor

Brigham Young University Office of IT

- Taught courses in HTML, CSS, Dreamweaver, InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Qualtrics, etc. to students, staff, and faculty.
- Developed curriculum for InDesign CS5 used in university-wide classes
- Created quick reference training cards for about 10 programs.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML CSS Javascript **LESS** PHP

Wordpress

Illustrator InDesign Photoshop Premiere Excel

PERSONAL SKILLS

Organization Project Management Training Collaboration

Documentation

EDUCATION

DevMountain

Web Development 2015

Brigham Young University

BA Design & New Media 2007-2012